[{"answer": "I did a couple of the love scenes.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "You never did that, did you?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Could you have ever imagined, when you were out there embedded with these troops, that that would happen?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "It is just a total distraction, isn't it?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think the idea -- the problem is that General Petraeus had an affair.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "First of all, I was substituting for George Stephanopoulos that Sunday as host of \"This Week.\"", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I can't get inside her brain.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Did she act in good faith, do you think?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Without question, as somebody who was covering the Benghazi story in the months leading up to the election, and also covering the election, it was so politicized with the White House and the administration in a defensive crouch, because they thought every word they said would be twisted and unfairly attacked.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "That's a problem, isn't it?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Do you think it's healthy for a biographer to be that close to their subject?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "ELLEY: Yes.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "But what would have happened, for example -- with one of your subjects, JFK -- what would have happened to JFK if e-mail and text messaging had existed?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "I think that's such a great question.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Does it matter if they have affairs?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Eliot Spitzer would come to mind.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Like whom?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "I don't think Churchill ever had affairs.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How about Churchill?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, the American media has come up with this narrative that he's the American hero who betrayed by the woman.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Why were you not a fan of General Petraeus?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I was worried about it because he's created again -- the military crossing into the CIA is very dangerous.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Were you surprised when Petraeus got the CIA job?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "In England, it is.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "-- for him to resign?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Very dangerous.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "That is quite dangerous, isn't it?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I'm pleased he won the election.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "On balance, are you pleased though that he won the election?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Boy.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Why did you want to make this series?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "I think he is tremendous.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "You thought it was really good?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I did a couple of the love scenes.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "You never did that, did you?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I'd actually go with my wife.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Of all the Bond girls, and there were so many, especially in the seven movies you made, if I could trap you on a desert island with one of them, and I know it is like choosing your favorite baby, but if I can put you on an island for the rest of your life with one Bond girl, who would it be?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I can say \"I love you\" in Swedish.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "But you get sort of used to it after you have said, \"my name is Bond, James Bond\" 400 times.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "I mean, to walk around with people knowing you're Bond?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, always.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Do people make you still say that?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Every interview.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Everywhere you go?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Been married four times.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "How many women do you think you have seduced because you played James Bond in the last 50 years?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I try to be.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "So you always just this nice, calm figure?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Depends what the definition of naughty is.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Have you been what British people would describe as a bit of a naughty boy over the years, would you say?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I suppose getting drunk, falling over and waking up in strange hotel rooms.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What would your definition be?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I regret I can't start them all again.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Do you have any regrets in your 85 years?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "You didn't hold that book up high enough.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Are you surprised that the Bond franchise is still so successful?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Are you surprised that it still -- I mean, even more successful than it was 50 years ago?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "I'm not going to answer anything political.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "You a fan of Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Because I work with UNICEF and you're not allowed with the United Nations.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that he, like Reagan, makes an American proud to be an American.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Do you feel that when you travel the world?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I suppose being with my parents when I did something that was worthwhile.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "If I could give you five minutes back of your entire life, and it can't involve marriage or children to relive, the greatest moment of your life, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Getting their love and respect?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "He was very happy.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "What would he have made of it?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Outnumbered.", "docId": "121118pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "That's basically been the story of your life ever since, isn't it, Sir Roger?", "qSentId": 632}]